http://www.dffcu.org/resources/terms-of-use-privacy-policy.html

Join
HOMEE-SERVICESOnline BankingEnroll NowMobile BankingRemote Deposit CaptureAgreementHelpful TipsE-statementsBill PayOnline UsageSecurity InformationSAVINGSSavings Account OptionsIRAsSavings RatesLOANSLoan Account OptionsVehicle LoansAuto Buying ServiceMortgagePersonal LoansVISAVISA DisclosureBusiness LoansStudent LoansShare Secured LoansDebt CancellationLoan RatesApply For a LoanCHECKINGChecking Account OptionsHealth Savings AccountsMasterMoney Debit CardOverdraft PrivilegeCheck ReorderChecking RatesKasasa Checking Cycle Date InformationRATESSavings RatesLoan RatesChecking RatesINVESTMENTSRESOURCESDispatch NewsMonarch Membership InfoSt. Helen Membership InfoAbout UsAuto LinkCalculatorsContact UsDiscount TicketsEmploymentFee ScheduleFinancial PlanningFinancial CounselingHours & LocationsKasasa Protect 24/7 Credit MonitoringWeb DisclaimerKasasa Checking Cycle Date InformationInsurance OptionsA&D InsuranceAuto, Home and much moreShared BranchingJoin UsTerms of Use & Privacy PolicyLINKSFree ATM Locator & Safety/Security TipsFirefighter LinksNewslettersCalendar
HOMEE-SERVICESOnline BankingEnroll NowMobile BankingRemote Deposit CaptureAgreementHelpful TipsE-statementsBill PayOnline UsageSecurity InformationSAVINGSSavings Account OptionsIRAsSavings RatesLOANSLoan Account OptionsVehicle LoansAuto Buying ServiceMortgagePersonal LoansVISAVISA DisclosureBusiness LoansStudent LoansShare Secured LoansDebt CancellationLoan RatesApply For a LoanCHECKINGChecking Account OptionsHealth Savings AccountsMasterMoney Debit CardOverdraft PrivilegeCheck ReorderChecking RatesKasasa Checking Cycle Date InformationRATESSavings RatesLoan RatesChecking RatesINVESTMENTSRESOURCESDispatch NewsMonarch Membership InfoSt. Helen Membership InfoAbout UsAuto LinkCalculatorsContact UsDiscount TicketsEmploymentFee ScheduleFinancial PlanningFinancial CounselingHours & LocationsKasasa Protect 24/7 Credit MonitoringWeb DisclaimerKasasa Checking Cycle Date InformationInsurance OptionsA&D InsuranceAuto, Home and much moreShared BranchingJoin UsTerms of Use & Privacy PolicyLINKSFree ATM Locator & Safety/Security TipsFirefighter LinksNewslettersCalendar
To access the Firefighters and Company Federal Credit Union's official privacy policy- download the PDF.
If you would like additional information on how we use your information and how to protect yourself, please read the information below: Firefighters and Company Federal Credit Union, your member owned financial institution, is committed to providing you with competitive products and services to meet your financial needs and help you reach your goals. We are equally committed to protecting the privacy of our members. Under federal law, we are required to give you a privacy notice. It describes our credit unions privacy policy and practices concerning the personal information we collect and disclose about our members. It also includes information about the parties who receive personal and sometimes nonpublic information from us as we conduct the business of the credit union. These practices are followed by the credit union. If after reading this notice you have questions, please contact us at:
(937) 228-1614
or write to:
Thomas L. NewtonFirefighters and Company Federal Credit Union338 South Patterson BoulevardDayton, OH 45402-2845
or email: staff@ffcocu.org
Information We Collect About You: We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:
Information about your transactions with us
Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency
Information obtained when verifying the information you provide on an application or other forms; this may be obtained from your current or past employers, or from other institutions where you conduct financial transactions
Internet website home financial services and e-mail
We may disclose all the information we collect, as described above, as permitted by law.
Parties Who Receive Information From Us: We may disclose nonpublic personal information about you to the following types of third parties:
Financial service providers, such as insurance companies, and mortgage service companies
Non-financial companies, such as consumer reporting agencies, data processors, check/share draft printers, plastic card processors, and government agencies
Disclosure of Information to Parties That Provide Services To Us: In order for us to conduct the business of the credit union, we may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to companies that perform marketing or other services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements so that we may provide members competitive products and services. We may also disclose nonpublic personal information about you under circumstances as permitted or required by law. These disclosures typically include information to process transactions on your behalf, conduct the operations of our credit union, follow your instructions as you authorize, or protect the security of our financial records.
To protect our members privacy, we only work with companies that agree to maintain strong confidentiality protections and limit the use of information we provide. We do not permit these companies to sell the information we provide to other third parties.
Disclosure of Information About Former Members: If you terminate your membership with Firefighters and Company Federal Credit Union, we will not share information we have collected about you, except as may be permitted or required by law.
How We Protect Your Information: We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, or procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information.
What Members Can Do To Help: Firefighters and Company Federal Credit Union is committed to protecting the privacy of its members. Members can help by following these simple guidelines:
Protect your account numbers, plastic card numbers, PINs (personal identification numbers) or passwords. Never keep your PIN with your card, which can provide free access to your accounts if your card is lost or stolen.
Use caution when disclosing your account numbers, social security numbers, etc. to other persons. If someone calls you explaining the call is on behalf of the credit union and asks for your account number, you should beware. Official credit union staff will have access to your information and will not need to ask for it.
Keep your information with us current. If your address or phone number changes, please let us know. It is important that we have current information on how to reach you. If we detect potentially fraudulent or unauthorized activity or use of an account, we will attempt to contact you immediately.
Let us know if you have questions. Please do not hesitate to call us, we are here to serve you!
*Promotional Disclosures
To report your debit card or credit card lost or stolen
MasterCard/HSA: Lost/Stolen   1-888-908-7835 VISA: Lost/Stolen 1-833-217-8094
Routing Number: 2422-7782-4
Terms of Use & Privacy Policy • Employment Opportunities • About Us
Download a PDF of the 2020 Printable Calendar
Firefighters & Company Federal Credit Union is committed to providing a website that is accessible to the widest possible audience in accordance with ADA standards and guidelines. If you are using a screen reader or other auxiliary aid and are having problems using this website, please contact us at 937-228-1614.
Firefighters & Company Federal Credit Union
